Chayanit Thawaranont

M.S. Student in Data Visualization

About Me

Hi! I'm Chayanit. A rising graduate student at Parsons School of Design. My main academic focus is Data Visualization. I'm a former product manager and a trend analyst. I'm now based in New York City.

Website Portfolio

LinkedIn

chayanit@newschool.edu

+16463394290

Skills

Design & Programming

Adobe CC	Javascript
Javascript	p5.js
CSS, Html	d3.js
Python	Figma
Power-Bi	Github
Tableau	SQL

Management

Design Thinking

Product Management

User Mapping

Research & Strategy

Trend Analysis

Qualitative Research

Quantitative Research

Users Research

UX design

UI planning

Experience

Product Manager @ Fashion Snoops, Trend Forecasting Agency

Feb 2020 - Oct 2021, New York City, NY, USA.

- Working closely on Al and Data analysis to deliver insights and report to our global users on a daily basis
- Reporting performance directly to CEO and managing the production team, and the direct team of 5 people.
- Monitoring platform through our backend and connecting with both editorial team and engineers to track more than 5,000 stores across global fashion retail market.
- Managing team and monitoring performance in the retail section.
- Setting up a satellite office in south east asia while coordinating with the headquarter in New York City.
- · Synchronising with sales team to win over clients in Thailand and expanding market shares.

Trend Analyst @ Fashion Snoops, Trend Forecasting Agency

Oct 2019 - Feb 2020, New York City, NY, USA.

- Copywrote reports and analyzed emerging trends in both macro and micro market.
- Oversaw Asian Pacific market updates to uncover market insights specifically in the region

Design Researcher @ Fire One One, Design Consultancy

May 2018 - Sep 2019, Bangkok, Thailand.

- Conducted strategic analysis and market research to decode key barriers of our client's business and recommend future position.
- Created presentation decks and pitched ideas directly to clients, suggesting new business approaches for clients.
- Researched trends by interviewing end users and find key insights to modify current business model in disrupted industries.

Creative Director @ Harvard College in Asia Program

Aug 2018 - May 2019, Boston, MA & Bangkok, Thailand.

- Planning activities schedule along with other committees for the annual conference which co-organized with Harvard University.
- Designing public announcement/information graphics which suitable with contents in each subject.

Education

Parsons School of Design, M.S. in Data Visualization.

Expected Graduation in May 2023, The New School, New York City, NY, USA.

Courses: Data Structure, Data Visualization & Information Aesthetic, Quantum Computing, Machine Learning, Visualizing Uncertainty, etc.

Chulalongkorn University, B.F.A. in Creative Arts.

Graduated in May 2019, Bangkok, Thailand.

Courses include: Decorative Arts, Design Thinking, Research & Report, Creative Design, etc.

Awards & Certification

Quantum Design Finalist / I.B.M

October 2021

Selected as one in four finalists from 20 teams at Parsons x IBM Quantum Jam, find more details at http://innovationcenter.newschool.edu/awards-teams/

CEO 1 MONTH Finalist / Adecco

October 2021

Selected as a finalist from 100+ talented youth in Thailand who participated in this competiition, find more details at https://www.adeccogroup.com/ceoforonemonth/

Credential Of Readiness Certificate / Harvard Business School

October 2019, Business Analytics, Economics for Managers, and Financial Accounting

CORe (Credential of Readiness) is a 150-hour certificate program on the fundamentals of business from Harvard Business School.